<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vietnam Endless beauty</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="favorite">Favorite</string>
    <string name="bookmark">Bookmark</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="chat">Chat</string>
    <string name="where_are_you_going">Where are you going?</string>
    <string name="e_g_ha_noi_viet_nam">E.g: Ha Noi, Viet Nam</string>
    <string name="place_to_visit">Place to visit: </string>
    <string name="hot_trend">Ranking</string>
    <string name="edit_profile">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="first_name">First name…</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last name…</string>
    <string name="password">Password…</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="welcome_back">Welcome back</string>
    <string name="enter_your_email">Enter your Email</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="forget_password">Forget password?</string>
    <string name="login_login">Login</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account">Don’t have an account?</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_onboard">Welcome to Onboard!</string>
    <string name="enter_your_full_name">Enter your full name</string>
    <string name="enter_confirm_password">Enter confirm Password</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="menu">Menu</string>
    <string name="general">General</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="enter_your_first_name">Enter your first name</string>
    <string name="enter_your_last_name">Enter your last name</string>
    <string name="need_to_fill">Need to fill in all information</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm the password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="account_error">Email or password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="update_success">Update Success</string>
    <string name="update_failed">Update Failed</string>
    <string name="description_hanoi">Vietnam is capital city is Hanoi. It is well-known for its many wonderful locations, cuisine, and the Hanoi people. Being born and raised in Hanoi makes me incredibly proud. A million people travel to Hanoi annually. Uncle Ho is Mausoleum, Hoa Lo Prison, Long Bien Bridge, One Pillar Pagoda, and many other places are popular tourist destinations in Hanoi. Each location has a special historical significance that is sacred. In regards to traffic, during the day, roads are congested with traffic, particularly during rush hours.</string>
    <string name="description_thaibinh">Thai Binh is a place with historical-cultural works and folklore activities, some of which have been listed by the government as Le Qui Don is worship hall, Ho Chi Minh is memento - house… but the most famous is Keo temple. Keo temple, also known as Than Quang temple, is a typical architectural work of Vietnam. A province has produced nearly 82 traditional festivals, 16 Vietnamese popular operas, and games such as cheo, roi nuoc, bat dat, and act.</string>
    <string name="description_haiphong">A significant Vietnamese seaport is located in Hai Phong, a sizable city. Hai Phong is close to the provinces of Quang Ninh to the north, Hai Duong to the west, and Thai Binh to the south. Inter-tropical monsoons have an impact on Hai Phong is weather because of its proximity to the East Sea. The annual mean temperature ranges from 23 to 24 °C. </string>
    <string name="description_quangninh">Quang Ninh is a land steeped in rich and ancient cultural traditions. The Ha long culture, which is considered a significant milestone in the evolution of Vietnamese culture, originated in this area. Like other provinces, the people of Quang Ninh have a diverse and vibrant culture. Buddhism has a long history in this region, with evidence of its practice dating back to before King Tran Thai Tong (1225–1258) came to Yen Tu Mountain to practice. Prior to his arrival, many religious figures had already been practicing in the area.</string>
    <string name="description_nghean">Nghe An Province benefits from its advantageous geographical location, with national highways, railways, the Cua Lo International Port, and Vinh Airport all within its borders. It is the starting point of both the Heritage route in the central part and the legendary Ho Chi Minh Trail, as well as the tourist route following the east-west corridor connecting Vinh - Laos - Thailand through Highway No. 8.</string>
    <string name="description_hochiminh">Saigon is a very populated city that seems to never sleep. The lifestyle here is constantly filled with interesting and novel things because this is a gathering place for many people from various cultural backgrounds across the nation. It is a tasteful blending of contemporary and traditional elements. Many small alleys with historically significant values can be found right behind taller buildings or in the middle of the city. People here put in a lot of work, but they also have a wonderful time.</string>
    <string name="description_quangbinh">I come from Dong Hoi, a small city in Quang Binh. My hometown is famous for many splendid caves such as Thien Duong, Phong Nha, Son Doong … Besides, there are also many beautiful beaches where you can enjoy many outdoor activities such as swimming, sunbathing. However, because of the sea pollution, many people like to swim in Moc stream. The weather here is not always pleasant. It usually rains heavily in autumn and is too hot in summer. However, you can go to my province during all seasons except autumn to avoid floods. The local people are friendly and helpful. In recent years, local tourism has developed to improve people isilives. I am very proud of my hometown and I hope you will have a trip to Quang Binh.</string>
    <string name="description_binhphuoc">Binh Phuoc is a province in the Southeast region, with 11 districts and towns. My hometown Binh Phuoc city is home to many beautiful historical scenes, such as: My Son Sanctuary, Dong Xoai Victory Monument, … And it has many attractive tourist attractions, such as: Ba Den Mountain, Garden Bu Gia Map Country, Ba Ra Mountain – Mo Waterfall, Bu Dang Rubber Forest. The weather here is very hot, there are 2 seasons: rainy season and dry season. Binh Phuoc is famous for cashew trees and rubber trees. The people here are very kind and gentle. And the food here is very good. This is a perfect place to visit and rest after tiring working hours. On weekends, if you have many times, you should come to this place to relax after a tiring time.</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>

    <string name="description_yentu">Yen Tu historical site is associated with the name of King Tran Nhan Tong, who led the army and people of the Tran dynasty to twice defeat the Yuan and Mongol armies, then renounced the throne, went to Yen Tu to practice, and founded the Zen sect. Truc Lam is rich in Vietnamese colors. Geographically, Yen Tu is a low mountain range, belonging to the Dong Trieu bow system, a geological region formed in the Quaternary period. The complex terrain and geology have created magnificent landscapes and traditional architecture blending into the majestic nature. Among them, it is impossible not to mention Yen Tu Pagoda. Located on the top of a mountain 1068m above sea level, the mountain top is always covered with clouds, adding a charming natural landscape, diverse and rich in flora and fauna. Surrounding the Yen Tu pagoda complex are famous relics and landscapes such as the West Yen Tu nature reserve, the Tran Dynasty historical site… To reach the top of Yen Tu, we must start with the stream Giai Oan and Giai Oan Pagoda. The Buddha Emperor himself gave the name Giai Oan to help save the maids who followed the king and committed suicide by jumping into the stream when the king did not allow them to serve them. Giai Oan Pagoda is famous for its sacredness, its back leans against a cliff, its face faces a gurgling stream day and night. Hoa Yen Pagoda is considered the main temple of the Yen Tu pagoda system. The pagoda resides halfway up the mountain, its position is very sturdy, and the scenery here is extremely beautiful. The pilgrimage road to Yen Tu peak has thousands of stone steps and rows of green trees on both sides of the road, with a huge canopy covering the road for everyone to travel. Nowadays, if we don not want to walk, we can take the cable car. The modern cable car system includes two stages, from the foot of the mountain to Hoa Yen Pagoda and from Hoa Yen Pagoda to Dong Pagoda.</string>
    <string name="description_halong">Ha Long Bay is a small bay on the west coast of the Gulf of Tonkin in the Northeast sea area of Vietnam, including the island waters of Ha Long city, Cam Pha town and part of Van Don island district. Ha Long Bay borders Cat Ba Island with a 120 km long coastline and nearly 2,000 large and small islands. About half of these islands have been named, the rest are largely wild, little explored and unnamed. There are two types of islands in Ha Long: limestone islands and schist islands, concentrated in two main regions: the southeast region of Bai Tu Long Bay and the southwest region of Ha Long Bay. Through the process of geological weathering here, nature has created a unique Ha Long in the world. The densely concentrated area of rocky islands with spectacular scenery and many famous beautiful caves is the central area of Ha Long Bay Natural Heritage, including Ha Long Bay and part of Bai Tu Long Bay.</string>
    <string name="description_baotang_quangninh">Quang Ninh Museum is a unique architectural and artistic work. Just looking from the outside makes visitors admire it. The museum is appearance is extremely attractive with black glass covering all sides. This is like a giant mirror reflecting the majestic image of Ha Long sea and sky. Besides, the museum is designed with a unique square structure with the main color black, which is also an image that makes many visitors think of black pearls - a precious product in Ha Long. Actually, the architecture of Quang Ninh museum is a delicate harmony between simple and modern, traditional but very new. In addition, the font appearing on the front along with the strangely designed zigzag staircase system has turned this Quang Ninh tourist destination into the most checked-in holy place in the mining land.</string>
    <string name="description_hotay">Ho Tay Lake is located in the northwest of Hanoi inner city with an area of about 500 hectares, the road around the lake is nearly 20km long. Historical geography has proven that the lake is a section of the Red River left behind, after changing course, for thousands of years. West Lake is also known as Mu Suong Lake (Dam Dam), Trau Vang Lake (Kim Nguu Lake), and Xa Cao Lake. Each name holds a story about the origin of the legendary West Lake. A French tourist named Michel said that this was his fourth time coming to Hanoi, but how many times he had been to West Lake, he could not even remember because West Lake was so beautiful and charming to him. heart. West Lake is the most romantic corner in the colorful picture of Hanoi; is a world of clear breezes, generosity and poetry. That is why for so long it has remained an endless source of inspiration for poets, writers, artists… with many songs and poems written about West Lake, written in West Lake that captivate people is hearts.</string>
    <string name="description_hoguom">Hoan Kiem Lake is one of the famous landscapes in our country. Hoan Kiem Lake is beautiful in paintings and photos, but outside it is even more beautiful. Located right in the heart of the capital, Hoan Kiem Lake has a beauty that is both magnificent and ancient, making people surprised. Blue sky, blue water, green trees. Everlasting green color covers the earth and sky all year round. All create a beautiful, vivid and harmonious picture. The surrounding streets are bustling with people. Different from the crowded and noisy city of Hanoi, Hoan Kiem Lake is more quiet, it has an ancient and peaceful beauty. Around the lake, trees grow luxuriantly, all of which are old trees and flowers that have been planted for many years. In the middle of the lake, on the green grass, the Turtle Tower stands out in ancient majesty. Turtle Tower is located on an empty space in the middle of the lake. The tower has three floors, small and mossy, located in the middle of a vast river. The tower is roof is curved, curved like a bird is wings flying against the blue sky. Many times people see turtles resting there. On the way to Ngoc Son Temple, we immediately recognize Pen Tower and Dai Nghien. The Pen Tower stands tall on a large mound of land. On the tower are three large red Chinese characters: Ta Thanh Thien, meaning "Writing on the blue sky" with the image of an inkstone and a brush nib symbolizing the studious spirit of the land of a thousand years of civilization.</string>
    <string name="description_thehuc">Traveling to Hanoi for 1 day, you should take the time to go to The Huc Bridge, which is curved like a shrimp and explore the unique architecture and meaning of this bridge. Previously, the bridge was made of rudimentary wood, but after the bridge breakage incident, Tham Hoang Tin - Mayor of Hanoi at that time, had the old bridge demolished and a new bridge rebuilt based on the architectural design. monk Nguyen Ngoc Diem. The bridge is designed in an arc shape and still retains 16 rows of piles. The bridge deck and walls are made of wood, but the horizontal and vertical beams are cast in concrete to ensure stability. According to legend, the bridge was built facing the East - towards the rising sun to fully receive oxygen. In particular, with the characteristic red color symbolizing life and happiness. The name The Huc means "bridge of the sun god".</string>

    <string name="description_chuakeo">Keo Pagoda is called "Than Quang Tu", located on the bank of Thai Binh River in Keo village, now Duy Nhat commune, Vu Thu district, Thai Binh province. People also call the pagoda in Thai Binh the Upper Keo, distinguishing it from the Lower Keo Pagoda in Nam Dinh, according to the flow of the river. Today is Keo Pagoda was built during the reign of King Le Trung Hung in 1632 in the "Foreign Noi Cong" architectural style typical of Vietnamese pagoda architecture (meaning the inside architecture is in the shape of the letter Cong, the outside is in the shape of the letter Cong). National letter shape). The entire temple campus is more than 41,500 square meters wide, including 16 architectural buildings with 116 construction spaces. In the temple grounds, there are 3 large lakes including the lake between the outer and inner three gates and two lakes behind the east and west corridors.</string>
    <string name="description_nhatho_thaibinh">Located on a land area of about 6,201.6 m2, Thai Binh Cathedral is designed in a modern architectural style, with many meanings from the Bible, while using designs and lines that are currently being used. Popular with local people. The cathedral is designed with two floors, with a total length of 81 meters, width of 24.5 meters, the widest part is 34.2 meters, including 18 meters of usable space and two large verandas. 3.25 meters long, the church is floor area is 2,260 m2. The upper floor of the church is used to celebrate Mass and liturgical ceremonies. The cathedral is dressed in a bright cream color, favoring alluvial colors, reminiscent of a rice countryside that once went down in history. Located in the basin of two large rivers, the Red River and Tra Ly River, Thai Binh is homeland has been nourished and nourished by a layer of fertile alluvium, helping Thai Binh once be the rice granary of the entire North of Vietnam. It is that land full of potential that has created Thai Binh people who are gentle, simple, patient and hard-working in everyday life but courageous in the challenges of faith.</string>
    <string name="description_tuongdai_bacho">Uncle Ho is monument with Vietnamese farmers is located in the architectural complex of Thai Binh Square. With all the harmonious and delicate lines, the image of Uncle Ho in simple clothes and a kind smile appears as if instructing generations of farmers to increase production and daily life to build build an increasingly civilized, prosperous and happy countryside. Responding to Uncle Ho is feelings, the group of statues includes characters representing generations of elderly people, middle-aged people, young people, and children in rural Vietnam attentively listening to his advice and instructions. Along with the group of statues, the front of the monument has 3 relief panels, showing typical landscapes of rural Vietnam, some activities of farmers, and village landscapes associated with the construction of new rural areas. . During his lifetime, Uncle Ho always wished for the lives of farmers to be prosperous and prosperous. Now, that has become a reality in every Vietnamese village in general, and Thai Binh in particular. On the back of the reliefs are images of craft village production, cultural activities, images of Keo pagoda, Tran temple festival, water puppet shows…, motifs that show typical nuances of Thai Binh culture.</string>
    <string name="description_catba">First, I would like to introduce Cat Ba with the most general information to tourists. Cat Ba is an archipelago belonging to Hai Phong city. Among them, the two largest islands are Cat Ba island and Cat Hai island. Cat Ba island district is about 30km from Hai Phong city center. Therefore, moving to Cat Ba is not too difficult, especially when winter traffic is increasingly developing. The district capital of Cat Ba island district is Cat Ba town. Currently, Cat Ba is a leading attractive natural, ecological and experiential tourism destination in the Northern region. Every year, this place attracts a large number of domestic and international tourists. In particular, Cat Ba Island is a world biosphere reserve recognized by UNESCO. This place has beautiful nature, diverse and rich ecosystems and extremely fresh air. Coming to Cat Ba Island will bring visitors interesting and new experiences and discoveries. In addition, Cat Ba Island is a place where people have lived for a long time. This is considered one of the cradles of ancient Vietnamese people with many important archaeological relics found. Cat Ba people are simple, gentle, naive and extremely hospitable. The beauty of nature, life and people blend perfectly to create a beautiful Cat Ba in the eyes of visitors. Therefore, Cat Ba becomes a top attractive tourist destination</string>
    <string name="description_dienchau">Dien Chau - A countryside with beautiful landscapes When talking about Dien Chau, we refer to a countryside with beautiful landscapes. Nature has rewarded this land with magnificent landscapes, enchanting beauty, with straight fields and fertile soil. Dien Chau Beach has beautiful bays that are convenient for boats to pass through. The air here is fresh. The mountains in Dien Chau are not high, the forests are not dense, the rivers and streams are not as many and large as other places, the mountains, forests and rivers of Dien Chau bear deep marks of history. The rivers, streams and mountains here have very beautiful scenery. It is a place of enjoyment for local and remote tourists. Dien Thanh Beach - Photo: Thanh Hai Through the bibliographies and records still kept in the State libraries, in the memories of people from all walks of life, Dien Chau district has beautiful scenery. great. Since ancient times, Dong Thanh district had 8 famous beautiful landscapes, Dien Chau mountain country today has up to 6 beautiful landscapes: 1. Da Son Linh Tich (sacred mark of Mo Da mountain) That is on the mountain range. There is An Duong Vuong Temple hidden in lush green forests. Behind the mountain is the vast sea, day and night whispering waves, every morning the sun rises from the sea. All scenery is covered with brilliant halo. To the north, at the foot of Mo Da mountain, is the historical Cua Hien, where there is a legend when An Duong Vuong and the god Kim Quy appeared holding a 7-inch long horn to part the water to take him to eternity. Cuong Temple - Photo: Thanh Hai 2. Bung Giang Thu Nguyet (autumn moon on Bung River) It is on bright moonlit autumn nights, the moonlight stretches long on the vast river surface, the sky is sparkling, the moon hovers in the air planted on the river bottom like a golden tray, making it difficult for visitors to worship the river scene to understand that wonderful feeling. 3. Bich Hai Quy Phung (sad wings about Cua Biec) Cua Biec means Cua Van where Bung River - the largest river of Dien Chau District flows into the East Sea.</string>
    <string name="description_doluong">The name Do Luong did not exist from the first days of building and defending the country, but until now this name has only been around for nearly 200 years. Standing on the highest peak of Buoc Troc mountain (208), looking towards the Quy Linh mountain range, we feel like we are lost in a fairyland, especially the lush green rice fields entering the ripening season, showing us Do Luong like a watercolor painting, or like a basin on all four sides are mountains and forests, in the middle are fields filled with fragrant countryside. Over thousands of years, people recruited people to establish hamlets, expanding the border until today. The tradition of solidarity in fighting against invaders to save the country and protect the homeland includes historical and revolutionary cultural works such as Truong Bon Victory Monument and Do Luong Uprising Monument. Each commune has memorial stele houses located in the center of 33 communes and towns, built in the period from 1990–1998 and basically completed, as a place for the people to commemorate and remember the merits of heroic martyrs. sacrificed for the independence, freedom and happiness of the People. Currently managing records: 4,036 martyrs, 3,448 wounded soldiers, 1,441 sick soldiers, 1,200 Dioxin agents, 262 Vietnamese mothers, 154 revolutionary veterans, 113 pre–uprising officers; 267 people were captured by the enemy; Do Luong has 18 heroic collectives of armed forces and 01 heroic commune of the reform period, 8 individuals of heroic people is armed forces, 12 outstanding teachers, 4 outstanding physicians, 05 outstanding artisans. There are 11 commanders who were promoted to generals in the army, police and border guards. The tradition of studiousness, good learning, passing and success is closely linked to the historical development of Confucianism in feudal Vietnam. Do Luong is tradition of studiousness and scholarship was also formed and developed. Along with the whole country at that time, the feudal system of schools and classrooms were mainly fourth–grade schools, opening and organizing teaching and learning in families and villages. In the history of academics during the Confucian period (1075–1919), Do Luong had 58 people who passed Bachelor is degree or higher, including 6 doctors, 1 Vice-table, 29 Huong tributes (like Bachelor is degrees) of the Le dynasty and 22 Bachelor is degrees. Nguyen Dynasty (History of Nghe An only records 57 people), ranked 7th out of 20 districts and cities of the province.</string>
    <string name="description_benthanh">Referring to Ho Chi Minh City, people mention Notre Dame Cathedral, the Independence Palace, Dam Sen, … and the most famous is Ben Thanh market. I do not know when Ben Thanh market has become an indispensable symbol when mentioning Saigon. Ben Thanh Market as well as Long Bien Bridge in Hanoi are witnesses to the ups and downs of the city, witnessing the changes and development of the city and the interaction between the past and present of the Saigon class. Ben Thanh Market was formed a long time ago, even before the first French people set foot in Gia Dinh. The origin of the market is a market originally located on the bank of Ben Nghe River, at a wharf near Gia Dinh citadel, so it was named Ben Thanh. From 1858 to 1911, the market operated quite bustlingly despite being occupied by the French. Then, due to a long period of use, the stalls in the market were old and could collapse at any time, so the market was partially demolished with plans to build a new one in another location. In 1911, the French moved the market to its current location, located between Phan Boi Chau, Phan Chau Trinh, Le Thanh Tong streets, Quach Thi Trang park in Ben Thanh ward, and built Ben Thanh market from a swamp. In 1912, construction began on the market until March 1913, when it was completed. Since then, Ben Thanh market has become a bustling market for traffickers and the people of Saigon.</string>
    <string name="this_application_is_written_by_tong_thien_quan_2023">2023 VietNamEndlessBeauty application contains materials sourced from Google, including images and information. All such materials are  not used for monetary purposes</string>
    <string name="description_phongnha_kebang">Phong Nha Ke Bang National Park is located in Quang Binh province. This is a place recognized by Unesco as a world natural heritage based on geological criteria in 2003. Moreover, in 2005, this place was recognized by Unesco as a world natural heritage in terms of ecology. Phong Nha Ke Bang is known as the cave kingdom with more than 3,000 large and small caves. Phong Nha cave is one of the three largest cave systems of Phong Nha- Ke Bang. Coming to Phong Nha Ke Bang, you will admire the most beautiful underground rivers, highest caves, sand dunes, and coral reefs, … It can be said that Phong Nha Ke Bang is the most attractive and charming tourist destination.</string>
    <string name="description_dinhdoclap">Ho Chi Minh City mesmerizes tourists by its modern skyline and colorful lights. Although the city has been recently renewed with a lot of magnificent buildings and trendy lifestyle, Saigon has still retained a visible and distinctive history. When it comes to Independence Palace or (Reunification Palace), its name does say what you want to know. As one of the finest colonial buildings in Saigon, it is considered not only the symbol of Vietnam national independence, but also a special national relic for its architectural and historical values. Built by the French during the period of 1868 and 1871, it originally served as the home and command center of Governor General. The palace was then taken over by Saigon government in 1954 (represented by President Ngo Dinh Diem) as well as renamed the Independence Palace. After being demolished by bombs in 1962, it was replaced by a new building.</string>
    <string name="google_maps_key" templateMergeStrategy="preserve" translatable="false">AIzaSyBZzlfwECTiVHrxyqL_olYyFrnnTyr4gXM</string>

</resources>